<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Canton Real Estate Video Blog with Amy Wengerd</title>
    <description>Our mission at The Amy Wengerd Group is to be your best resource for Canton real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The The Amy Wengerd Group, your professional Canton Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://soldbyamyblog.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 11:55:08 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 11:55:08 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Summary of How Our Recasting Program Works</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/v4aqMA6xmAA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;Homeowners: have you heard of recasting? If not, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to see today&amp;rsquo;s post.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a homeowner who wants to buy a home before selling your current one, you’ll definitely want to hear about our Recasting Program. Here’s how it works:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say that you qualified to carry both your new home and your current home mortgages. Let’s also say that you don’t want to sell your home until you know that you have a place to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=So many people have benefited from this program.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/a-summary-of-how-our-recasting-program-works.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“So many people have benefited from this program.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under our recasting program, &lt;strong&gt;our lenders will allow you to purchase the new home with the minimum down payment,&lt;/strong&gt; and when your current home closes, you can apply whatever amount you’d like to your new mortgage payment. Even more than that, once you apply the amount toward your mortgage, you could then have that payment adjusted down to reflect the new mortgage balance without adjusting the term or interest rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So many people have benefited from this program and we wanted to make sure that you had this information at your disposal, as well. Consider this just another tool in your pocket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this or other programs that we offer, go ahead and reach out to us. We’d love to meet with you to help you make the best real estate decisions for your situation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/a-summary-of-how-our-recasting-program-works.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/a-summary-of-how-our-recasting-program-works.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Top 5 Reasons Homebuyers Should Hire an Exclusive Buyer Specialist</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jftxkc2cBbE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;Here are the top five reasons that homebuyers should hire an exclusive buyer specialist to assist them in their purchase.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Amy Wengerd Group has created an exclusive group of buyer specialists who are not only licensed Realtors, but who have also gone through extensive additional training before ever even serving one of our clients. Here are the top five reasons that homebuyers should hire an exclusive buyer specialist:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Sellers have exclusive representation of their own&lt;/strong&gt;, so why shouldn’t you as a buyer? The seller has hired and contracted an agent to get them the most money out of their house in any given market. However, as a buyer, you want to get the best deal (i.e., the lowest price) for a home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Buyer representation is virtually free.&lt;/strong&gt; Most agencies will charge a buyer anywhere from $200 to $500 for their services to be paid at closing. The seller always pays the commission of the agent who represents you, so you don’t have to worry about paying a commission. You’ll typically only have to pay a small fee to the brokerage, but the amount of help you receive in return is invaluable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The seller always pays the commission of the agent who represents you, so you don’t have to worry about paying a commission.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/the-top-5-reasons-homebuyers-should-hire-an-exclusive-buyer-specialist.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The seller always pays the commission of the agent who represents you, so you don’t have to worry about paying a commission.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. You only need to call your buyer specialist when you have a question about a listing.&lt;/strong&gt; They can answer all of your questions, show you any house, advise you on the market, and so much more. Wouldn’t that be so much easier than clicking through all the different websites and contacting numerous Realtors about all the different properties, waiting for the calls back, and trying to figure out which Realtor called you about which house? It gets a little overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Our buyer clients enjoy certain benefits&lt;/strong&gt;, like being able to use our moving truck for free and receiving a discount card. Plus, they have a team helping out who make sure the buyers never miss out on the home of their dreams. They’ll also receive invitations to our special events, giveaways, and so much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Year to date, our buyer agents have saved their clients over $543,000 on their home purchases.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact us today so you can get started. Let us help you make the perfect match with one of our buyer specialists so we can get you into your dream home this year—there’s still plenty of time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 14:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/the-top-5-reasons-homebuyers-should-hire-an-exclusive-buyer-specialist.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/the-top-5-reasons-homebuyers-should-hire-an-exclusive-buyer-specialist.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Tell if Your Home Is Overpriced</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fq3VBQ7Ta08?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;There are three ways you can tell if your home is overpriced.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many homeowners come to us to voice their frustration that their home hasn’t sold, and almost every time, the reason why boils down to overpricing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We at the Amy Wengerd Group always try to get the most money possible for our sellers no matter which market we’re in, and sometimes they prefer to list their house above our suggested price, and that’s fine. But what if you picked an agent with a great reputation and marketing plan and your home still isn’t selling?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the three ways to know if your home is overpriced:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. No buyers or Realtors are contacting you about the house.&lt;/strong&gt; This means no emails, texts, phone calls, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You always want to net the most money possible from your home sale, but you don’t want to sabotage it by pricing your home too high.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-to-tell-if-your-home-is-overpriced.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You always want to net the most money possible from your home sale, but you don’t want to sabotage it by pricing your home too high.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Your home has showings, but no offers.&lt;/strong&gt; In this situation, you’ll hear buyers tell you that they’d like to keep looking, or the house just isn’t for them, or they found something they liked better. Usually, this means they liked what they saw online, but they decided the home wasn’t a good value in person. In other words, you’re helping to sell the competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Potential buyers are making lowball offers.&lt;/strong&gt; This doesn’t mean they want to “steal your house.” They may like it, but feel as though the price doesn’t align with current market conditions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You always want to net the most money possible from your home sale, but you don’t want to sabotage it by pricing your home too high. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like some guidance on how to navigate this tricky process, don’t hesitate to give our team a call. We’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 09:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-to-tell-if-your-home-is-overpriced.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-to-tell-if-your-home-is-overpriced.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Reasons Our Fast Forward Program Might Be Your Best Option</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fTkbZjz6l8w?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an investor or a homeowner, our Fast Forward Program may be perfect for you. Here&amp;rsquo;s why.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investors and homeowners, take note: My team is having so much success that we want to remind you once more about the newest program we’re offering to you. It’s called the Fast Forward Program, and we’ve had numerous home sellers already take advantage of it. &lt;strong&gt;There are four reasons, specifically, why this program may be your best option. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. You need a fast sale and don’t have time to wait for an offer.&lt;br /&gt;2. You don’t want to deal with the home showings and everything else that comes with the typical home sale process.&lt;br /&gt;3. Time is more important to you than getting top dollar. &lt;br /&gt;4. You have equity in your house and need to sell now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This is just one more way the Amy Wengerd Group is making it easy for sellers and investors to achieve success in any market.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/4-reasons-our-fast-forward-program-might-be-your-best-option.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This is just one more way the Amy Wengerd Group is making it easy for sellers and investors to achieve success in any market.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re an investor, you need to call my team and me now, because we know how hard it is to find the right properties and compete against other investors to purchase them. As one of our investors, we’ll let you know which houses we have that fit your criteria. It’s an easy purchasing process, and you get to pick the closing date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just one more way the Amy Wengerd Group is making it easy for sellers and investors to achieve success in any market. If you have any questions about this program or have any other real estate needs we can help you with, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. &lt;strong&gt;Certain restrictions apply.&lt;/strong&gt; I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 12:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/4-reasons-our-fast-forward-program-might-be-your-best-option.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/4-reasons-our-fast-forward-program-might-be-your-best-option.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Should You Fix in Your Home to Get Top Dollar?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/SjqFcv_53OM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Before you put your home on the market, there are four repairs and upgrades you should make to ensure you earn top dollar.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making certain upgrades and repairs to your home before you list it is a good idea, in general, but did you know that doing so can also help you earn top dollar? Here are four key projects most likely to bring a high return: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Improve and maintain your home’s curb appeal.&lt;/strong&gt; The way your home looks when buyers pull up to it on the street will serve as their first (in-person) impression, so you need to make sure it’s a good one. Trim trees and bushes, add fresh mulch, and plant a few flowers to get everything looking neat and inviting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Take care of minor repairs you’ve been putting off.&lt;/strong&gt; If you’ve always meant to touch up your paint or fix that hole in your siding, now is the time to do so. Buyers are going to notice every little thing when they look at your home, so make sure there aren’t many issues for them to find before your home goes live on the market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Buyers will be able to better envision how they might utilize your home’s space after it’s been decluttered.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/what-should-you-fix-in-your-home-to-get-top-dollar.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Buyers will be able to better envision how they might utilize your home’s space after it’s been decluttered.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Declutter.&lt;/strong&gt; Cluttered homes look smaller and less clean than they may actually be, which can deter buyers. So as you get ready to sell your home, start packing away, selling, or trashing unwanted items. Your home will look much better once you do. Beyond that, buyers will be able to better envision how they might utilize your home’s space. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Make sure expensive systems and appliances are functioning properly.&lt;/strong&gt; The last thing you want is to go under contract only for the buyer to find out your HVAC unit isn’t functioning properly. These are the sort of problems that home inspections are designed to identify, and leaving them unresolved could cost you your deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 09:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/what-should-you-fix-in-your-home-to-get-top-dollar.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/what-should-you-fix-in-your-home-to-get-top-dollar.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Scenarios Where Our Fast Forward Program Might Be Your Best Option</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5L2F59qs36M?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;  Looking to sell a home? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epropertywatch.com/homeownerPage/x4w8Ojzn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;  Looking to buy a home? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amysguarantee.com/search&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is the Fast Forward program the best option for your own selling goals? It just might be if:  As many of you know, The Amy Wengerd Group unveiled our Fast Forward program for home sellers earlier this year. We’re excited to report that it’s been a resounding success as we’ve been able to serve so many of our clients with it already. In fact, we just closed on a client’s house today! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. You want to skip the traditional sale process. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. You prefer to have an immediate sale. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. You prioritize time over your home’s sale price. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. You don’t want to list your home online or have people walk through it. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in pursuing one of these selling options, we’d be happy to have one of our listing specialists meet with you and go more in depth about what this program entails. If you like what you hear, we’ll make an offer on your home within 72 hours of our initial meeting. It’s that simple: no hassle, no showings, no waiting for a buyer to come along. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=It’s that simple: no hassle, no showings, no waiting for a buyer to come along.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/4-scenarios-where-our-fast-forward-program-might-be-your-best-option.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“It’s that simple: no hassle, no showings, no waiting for a buyer to come along.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to sell your home the traditional way, we can help with that too and we promise equally amazing results. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like more information, please reach out to us today so we can find out which method is most appropriate for your situation. We look forward to hearing from you! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 15:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/4-scenarios-where-our-fast-forward-program-might-be-your-best-option.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/4-scenarios-where-our-fast-forward-program-might-be-your-best-option.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Things That Affect the Length of Your Home Purchase</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DxE2Djp5cA4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through assisting so many clients, we’ve gained a thorough understanding of what confuses buyers most about the real estate process. &lt;strong&gt;Here are three key things to remember to make your buying experience a success:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. The process may take longer than you think.&lt;/strong&gt; On average, it can take one to three months for a buyer to find a home that they like. That’s assuming that all the good houses are available and not flying off the market like they did this last spring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=It could take five months or more from start to finish.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-things-that-affect-the-length-of-your-home-purchase.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“It could take five months or more from start to finish.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once your offer is accepted, the bank will take approximately 40 days to process and approve your loan.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The homeowner may ask for additional time to stay in the house after closing.&lt;/strong&gt; This is negotiable, but it should be something that you account for when you’re calculating your timeline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, it could take four to five months for you to get into your new home when all is said and done. &lt;strong&gt;If you want to be in your new home by the holidays, you should give us a call today to get the process started.&lt;/strong&gt; We’ll make sure it’s as smooth and fun as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions for me about buying a home or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 12:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-things-that-affect-the-length-of-your-home-purchase.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-things-that-affect-the-length-of-your-home-purchase.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can Our Guaranteed Sale Program Benefit You?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/c7Px8jXxpnE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We at The Amy Wengerd Group have been offering our Guaranteed Sale Program to our clients for more than six years. Much to their satisfaction, we recently helped seven clients sell their home using this very program. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But how will you know if this program is right for you? Here are five scenarios where our Guaranteed Sale Program is just what the doctor ordered: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. You want to make an offer on a new home without worrying about the sale of your current home &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. You want to know what you can expect and what you’ll net from your sale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. You want to know that your home will sell in 59 days or less &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. You want the freedom to make solid plans and not worry about your sale &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. You have equity in your home and want the peace of mind that comes with a sale  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Your goals are our goals.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/can-our-guaranteed-sale-program-benefit-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Your goals are our goals.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bottom line is we’ll strive to get you the most money out of your sale, whether it’s through a traditional channel, our Guaranteed Sale Program, or our new instant offer program, your goals are our goals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like to meet with one of our seller specialists to learn the specifics of our program, please give me or my team a call today. We look forward to serving you!  &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 09:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/can-our-guaranteed-sale-program-benefit-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/can-our-guaranteed-sale-program-benefit-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are Home Inspections Worth It?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RVTSB7Q28is?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Homebuyers often ask if it’s worth it to spend the money to hire a professional home inspector. As it turns out, there are three key reasons why you should engage the services of an experienced inspector before you buy a home:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. You’ll gain a better understanding of your new home.&lt;/strong&gt; Not only does a home inspector point out issues of concern, but they also answer any and all questions you might have about the systems in the house. Every house is different, so making sure that you have a good understanding of your new home is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. They’ll find both current and future issues with the home.&lt;/strong&gt; A home inspector won’t just find issues that currently beset the property, but they can also tell you which issues are most likely to arise in the future. It’s a really good idea to start a plan for home improvements in the future if you don’t want to be blindsided by costly repairs down the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Without the inspector’s report, it’s virtually impossible for us to address any repair issues with the homeowner.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/are-home-inspections-worth-it.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Without the inspector’s report, it’s virtually impossible for us to address any repair issues with the homeowner.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Home inspections will allow us to negotiate home repairs with the seller.&lt;/strong&gt; A great inspector will provide you with a thorough report, complete with pictures and details, within 24 hours of your inspection. Without that report, it’s virtually impossible for us to address any repair issues with the homeowner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter what, we want to make sure that our homebuyers have the most information available when undergoing what is likely the largest investment of their lives. We work with some of the best home inspectors in the area, and we can even help you purchase a home warranty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in need of assistance in your next real estate purchase, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. One of our buyer specialists will be happy to get you started on the right track.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 12:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/are-home-inspections-worth-it.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/are-home-inspections-worth-it.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Our Team Utilizes Social Media to Boost Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NjeEj7YGBHg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t heard by now, “Rambo 5: Last Blood” is coming to theaters in September. Anyone who knows me is aware that I’m a huge fan of Sylvester Stallone’s, and I’m apparently not the only one—the movie is being promoted all over social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of social media: 15 years ago when Facebook started, who would have thought that we’d end up selling homes on Facebook? The internet has changed drastically in a relatively short period of time, and being mindful of your social media presence is key in our business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/SOLDBYWENGERD/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amy Wengerd Group’s Facebook page&lt;/a&gt; currently has over 2,300 followers, and that number grows every day.&lt;/strong&gt; Each year on one of our social media sites, we give away almost $1,000 in prizes, and this doesn’t include all of our past client giveaways and the events that we hold for those past clients. Some of our real estate posts have reached over 20,000 people and have been shared hundreds of times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Some of our real estate posts have reached over 20,000 people and have been shared hundreds of times.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-our-team-utilizes-social-media-to-boost-business.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Some of our real estate posts have reached over 20,000 people and have been shared hundreds of times.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/amywengerdrealestateteam&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; to network with other professionals in the area to help our business grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/soldbywengerd/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; works best for our younger buyers and sellers. Here, we recruit, sell homes, post giveaways, share stories, and help our clients harness the power of social media. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By following us on all our sites, you’ll allow us to help even more people, and hopefully, you’ll win something along the way.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about utilizing social media to empower your business, please don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 11:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-our-team-utilizes-social-media-to-boost-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-our-team-utilizes-social-media-to-boost-business.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
