<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Canton Real Estate Video Blog with Amy Wengerd</title>
    <description>Our mission at The Amy Wengerd Group is to be your best resource for Canton real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The The Amy Wengerd Group, your professional Canton Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://soldbyamyblog.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 11:04:27 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 11:04:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Things That Affect the Length of Your Home Purchase</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DxE2Djp5cA4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through assisting so many clients, we’ve gained a thorough understanding of what confuses buyers most about the real estate process. &lt;strong&gt;Here are three key things to remember to make your buying experience a success:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. The process may take longer than you think.&lt;/strong&gt; On average, it can take one to three months for a buyer to find a home that they like. That’s assuming that all the good houses are available and not flying off the market like they did this last spring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=It could take five months or more from start to finish.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-things-that-affect-the-length-of-your-home-purchase.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“It could take five months or more from start to finish.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once your offer is accepted, the bank will take approximately 40 days to process and approve your loan.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The homeowner may ask for additional time to stay in the house after closing.&lt;/strong&gt; This is negotiable, but it should be something that you account for when you’re calculating your timeline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, it could take four to five months for you to get into your new home when all is said and done. &lt;strong&gt;If you want to be in your new home by the holidays, you should give us a call today to get the process started.&lt;/strong&gt; We’ll make sure it’s as smooth and fun as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions for me about buying a home or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 12:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-things-that-affect-the-length-of-your-home-purchase.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-things-that-affect-the-length-of-your-home-purchase.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can Our Guaranteed Sale Program Benefit You?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/c7Px8jXxpnE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We at The Amy Wengerd Group have been offering our Guaranteed Sale Program to our clients for more than six years. Much to their satisfaction, we recently helped seven clients sell their home using this very program. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But how will you know if this program is right for you? Here are five scenarios where our Guaranteed Sale Program is just what the doctor ordered: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. You want to make an offer on a new home without worrying about the sale of your current home &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. You want to know what you can expect and what you’ll net from your sale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. You want to know that your home will sell in 59 days or less &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. You want the freedom to make solid plans and not worry about your sale &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. You have equity in your home and want the peace of mind that comes with a sale  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Your goals are our goals.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/can-our-guaranteed-sale-program-benefit-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Your goals are our goals.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The bottom line is we’ll strive to get you the most money out of your sale, whether it’s through a traditional channel, our Guaranteed Sale Program, or our new instant offer program, your goals are our goals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like to meet with one of our seller specialists to learn the specifics of our program, please give me or my team a call today. We look forward to serving you!  &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 09:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/can-our-guaranteed-sale-program-benefit-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/can-our-guaranteed-sale-program-benefit-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are Home Inspections Worth It?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RVTSB7Q28is?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Homebuyers often ask if it’s worth it to spend the money to hire a professional home inspector. As it turns out, there are three key reasons why you should engage the services of an experienced inspector before you buy a home:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. You’ll gain a better understanding of your new home.&lt;/strong&gt; Not only does a home inspector point out issues of concern, but they also answer any and all questions you might have about the systems in the house. Every house is different, so making sure that you have a good understanding of your new home is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. They’ll find both current and future issues with the home.&lt;/strong&gt; A home inspector won’t just find issues that currently beset the property, but they can also tell you which issues are most likely to arise in the future. It’s a really good idea to start a plan for home improvements in the future if you don’t want to be blindsided by costly repairs down the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Without the inspector’s report, it’s virtually impossible for us to address any repair issues with the homeowner.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/are-home-inspections-worth-it.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Without the inspector’s report, it’s virtually impossible for us to address any repair issues with the homeowner.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Home inspections will allow us to negotiate home repairs with the seller.&lt;/strong&gt; A great inspector will provide you with a thorough report, complete with pictures and details, within 24 hours of your inspection. Without that report, it’s virtually impossible for us to address any repair issues with the homeowner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter what, we want to make sure that our homebuyers have the most information available when undergoing what is likely the largest investment of their lives. We work with some of the best home inspectors in the area, and we can even help you purchase a home warranty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in need of assistance in your next real estate purchase, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. One of our buyer specialists will be happy to get you started on the right track.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 12:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/are-home-inspections-worth-it.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/are-home-inspections-worth-it.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Our Team Utilizes Social Media to Boost Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/NjeEj7YGBHg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t heard by now, “Rambo 5: Last Blood” is coming to theaters in September. Anyone who knows me is aware that I’m a huge fan of Sylvester Stallone’s, and I’m apparently not the only one—the movie is being promoted all over social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of social media: 15 years ago when Facebook started, who would have thought that we’d end up selling homes on Facebook? The internet has changed drastically in a relatively short period of time, and being mindful of your social media presence is key in our business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/SOLDBYWENGERD/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amy Wengerd Group’s Facebook page&lt;/a&gt; currently has over 2,300 followers, and that number grows every day.&lt;/strong&gt; Each year on one of our social media sites, we give away almost $1,000 in prizes, and this doesn’t include all of our past client giveaways and the events that we hold for those past clients. Some of our real estate posts have reached over 20,000 people and have been shared hundreds of times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Some of our real estate posts have reached over 20,000 people and have been shared hundreds of times.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-our-team-utilizes-social-media-to-boost-business.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Some of our real estate posts have reached over 20,000 people and have been shared hundreds of times.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/amywengerdrealestateteam&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; to network with other professionals in the area to help our business grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/soldbywengerd/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; works best for our younger buyers and sellers. Here, we recruit, sell homes, post giveaways, share stories, and help our clients harness the power of social media. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By following us on all our sites, you’ll allow us to help even more people, and hopefully, you’ll win something along the way.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about utilizing social media to empower your business, please don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 11:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-our-team-utilizes-social-media-to-boost-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-our-team-utilizes-social-media-to-boost-business.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comparing Our Market Between the First Half of 2018 and 2019</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/eC9zGm4v44A?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re at about the halfway point of 2019, which means it’s the perfect time to bring you an update on our local market. &lt;strong&gt;Today we’ll compare the numbers from January 1 to June 15 of 2018 against the numbers from that same period this year. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first half of 2018, Stark County had 1,967 sales compared to 1,869 sales up to this point in 2019—a 5% drop year over year.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The average price per square foot was $83 in 2018 and increased to $87 between January and mid-June this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Days on market remained relatively unchanged with 2018’s first half being 73 days and 2019’s first half being 70 days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=These numbers are a signal that sellers in Stark or Summit County still have a lot to gain from our current market.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/comparing-our-market-between-the-first-half-of-2018-and-2019.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“These numbers are a signal that sellers in Stark or Summit County still have a lot to gain from our current market.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The average sale price between June January and June 2018 was $146,432 and rose to $154,948. That’s a 12% increase year over year for Stark County. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halfway through 2018 in Summit County, there were 3,244 sales compared to 3,008 sales up to this point in 2019—a 7.3% drop year over year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The average price per square foot was $94 in 2018 and increased to $99 between January and mid-June this year. That amounts to $8,500 more to the average Summit County homeowner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for days on market, Summit County homes spent an average of 81 days on market in the first half of 2018 versus 72 days in 2019.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The average sale price between June January and June 2018 was $162,193 and rose to $171,267. That’s a 5% appreciation rate for homes in Summit County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite fewer sales, both the price per square foot and average sale price have increased, which signals that sellers in Stark or Summit County still have a lot to gain from our current market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like a personalized market analysis of your home, please let us know! And have a great summer! &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 09:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/comparing-our-market-between-the-first-half-of-2018-and-2019.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/comparing-our-market-between-the-first-half-of-2018-and-2019.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Absorption Rate Data Informs Our Team’s Approach</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6XiZGjMFP9Y?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, I’m holding a stack of papers, and printed on these papers are &lt;strong&gt;absorption rates&lt;/strong&gt; that we track week to week. To better understand the market’s state at a given time, many buyers and sellers come to us asking about supply and demand in their particular area. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Absorption rate data is divided into area, county, and the townships and cities located within them. Let’s explore how instrumental this data is in serving our clients a little further: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year in North Canton, there was just a one month’s supply of homes in the $200,000 to $300,000 price range. Fast forward to 2019: We now have a three-month supply of homes in that same price range. With respect to those homes, this points to a slowdown in sales and more inventory from one year to the next.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=By careful comparison and analysis of absorption rate data, we can advise both our buyers and sellers based on the numbers for that particular week.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-absorption-rate-data-informs-our-teams-approach.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“By careful comparison and analysis of absorption rate data, we can advise both our buyers and sellers based on the numbers for that particular week.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all that in mind, we’ll advise our sellers whose home falls within that price point to yield to these conditions and to lean more toward a competitive pricing strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for our buyers, we’ll share the encouraging news that there are more homes available in that price range than there were just a year earlier. We can also show them the data for the $300,000 to $350,000 range and, in this particular case, it only gets better: Inventory jumps from a three-month supply to a 7.5-month supply. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of this is made possible by absorption rate data, and &lt;strong&gt;by careful comparison and analysis, we can advise both our buyers and sellers based on the numbers for that particular week.&lt;/strong&gt; No matter if you’re a buyer or seller, please reach out to us and let us put our experience and expertise to work for you. We hope to hear from you very soon!  &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 10:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-absorption-rate-data-informs-our-teams-approach.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/how-absorption-rate-data-informs-our-teams-approach.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Ways We’ll Help You Buy &amp; Sell a Home All at Once</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VrPJf8SAP-c?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps simultaneously buying a new home and selling your current home is an approach that lines up with your real estate goals. If that’s the case, there are three solutions to help you maneuver through the process smoothly: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speak with a reputable lender to learn all your options first.&lt;/strong&gt; Your lender may reveal that you have enough equity in your current home to extract and use as a down payment on your new home—what’s known as a bridge loan. We have lenders who can help you with this option. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re selling first, place a contingency offer on your new home.&lt;/strong&gt; With this contingency, any purchase you make hinges on the sale of your current home. Until then, you’re not obligated to go through with buying a home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Your lender may reveal that you have enough equity in your current home to extract and use as a down payment on your new home.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-ways-well-help-you-buy-sell-a-home-all-at-once.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Your lender may reveal that you have enough equity in your current home to extract and use as a down payment on your new home.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will also allow us to extend the closing date on your purchase if necessary. Say our original closing date is set for May 25, which would mean your first payment is scheduled for July 1. By extending your closing date to June 1, though, your first payment won’t be due until August 1—that one extra week gives us a much larger window of time to sell your home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;strong&gt;sell your home through our exclusive guaranteed sale program.&lt;/strong&gt; You’ve heard it on the radio and we’ve said it for years: If we can’t sell your home through the traditional course in 59 days or less, we will buy the home ourselves. You’ll be made aware of the buyout price and any fees up front so you can plan for your next purchase without any uncertainty about your home sale. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if you’re already eyeing a property you love, and you’d like to make a speedy sale? No worries! We can even give you an instant offer on your home, in which you can set the closing date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, we have just about every situation covered for your specific buyer and seller needs. Just reach out to us. We’d be happy to help! &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 12:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-ways-well-help-you-buy-sell-a-home-all-at-once.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/3-ways-well-help-you-buy-sell-a-home-all-at-once.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Top 3 Mistakes That Can Sabotage Your Home Sale</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/KPOi0uwNVoE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the time of year that homeowners begin asking me questions about selling their home for the most possible money. If selling for the most is your goal, here are three major mistakes that you should avoid making, lest you risk potentially sabotaging your own sale:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Setting the wrong price.&lt;/strong&gt; Overpricing isn’t the only mistake a seller should avoid making; you should also avoid underpricing your home—it may cause them to think that something is wrong with your home. Of course, overpricing can push away buyers who think your home is too expensive. That’s why hiring an experienced agent can save you thousands of dollars and lots of grief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The more buyers that we can expose your home to early on, the better the chances we have of presenting you with a great offer early on.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/the-top-3-mistakes-that-can-sabotage-your-home-sale.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The more buyers that we can expose your home to early on, the better the chances we have of presenting you with a great offer early on.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Failing to prepare your home for sale.&lt;/strong&gt; One of the first things we have to do when selling your home is list it online to the hundreds of different websites where we market homes. That means it’s very important to spend time decluttering, neutralizing, and revamping your curb appeal to make it look its best when our photographer comes to your home. Great listing photos will increase the number of showings you get, which then greatly increases your chances of getting a great offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Turning down showing requests.&lt;/strong&gt; Requests to view your home may not always come at the most convenient time, but the more buyers that we can expose your home to early on, the better the chances we have of presenting you with a great offer early on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking of selling your home, reach out to us. Let’s set up a private tour of your home where we can create a home selling strategy tailored specifically to you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 11:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/the-top-3-mistakes-that-can-sabotage-your-home-sale.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/the-top-3-mistakes-that-can-sabotage-your-home-sale.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Kind of Home Sale Is Right for You?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kj0zmeG9pBY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current spring market is already shaping up to be quite lively, so if you’ve been thinking of putting your home on the market this year, now may be the perfect time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With inventory at just three months’ worth of homes in both Stark and Summit County and rates currently at an incredible 4.25% for 30-year fixed mortgages, it’s no wonder why buyers are coming out in droves. As a seller, this means you’ve got a fantastic window of opportunity before you. High demand equates to more money in your pocket, after all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you’re considering a sale, why not let our team help maximize your success? There are three different ways we can help you sell:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Our traditional sale.&lt;/strong&gt; This method is the one we use most. It implements our award-winning, nationally recognized marketing plan, and has been specifically designed to help you sell quickly and for top dollar. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Our goal is to help you sell in a way that best suits your needs.%20https://soldbyamyblog.com/what-kind-of-home-sale-is-right-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Our goal is to help you sell in a way that best suits your needs.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Our guaranteed sale.&lt;/strong&gt; If we can’t buy your home within 59 days, we’ll buy it from you directly for a price you agree on up front. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Our instant offer.&lt;/strong&gt; This third method, which is also the latest addition to our repertoire, eliminates the hassle of a traditional selling experience. If you’d rather avoid listing your home on the open market, we’d be happy to make an offer on your home ourselves. All it takes is a simple meeting to talk about your goals. Within 72 hours of that meeting, we’ll present you with an offer and get moving on your home sale. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever option you choose, our goal is to help you sell in a way that best suits your needs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me or my team a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 11:28:41 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/what-kind-of-home-sale-is-right-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/what-kind-of-home-sale-is-right-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Need a Free Roof Inspection?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/oT05C2jQQSM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of you probably remember that crazy windstorm we experienced a couple weeks ago. If so, let me ask you: Have you had your roof checked out since then? Unless the wind visibly damaged your home, you probably haven’t thought about it much. The good news is that we know of a company who will do a free roof inspection for you, inform you if your roof did, in fact, suffer wind damage, and tell you if you are eligible to get a new roof by filing an insurance claim. The message is just another way that we help make sure our homeowners are getting the best possible customer service. If you’d like to take advantage of this opportunity, all you need to do is reach out to us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 09:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://soldbyamyblog.com/need-a-free-roof-inspection.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://soldbyamyblog.com/need-a-free-roof-inspection.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
